Welcome my fellow Georgia enthusiasts to Georgia World in Yokohama and today I'm gonna be taking you all around
Georgia World you'll be thinking kind of what is there possibly to do well don't worry
I should be finding out everything you need to know in the video today now you might hear the word world and think a giant theme park
But now it's more of a Disney's store-esque style and a shopping mall in Yokohama Japan
So I'm gonna walk you through everything there is to do here today and hopefully keep you entertained
And if you're not a Georgia fan you might be very confused
But if you love Georgia you're gonna want to see this video so without further ado, let's get into it
So yeah, maybe you guys don't care maybe you do but I give them a little back in for how I found out about this
Basically on Twitter the official Georgia account kept retweeting something about this
Georgia world happening in Yokohama and I was like okay well
I'm literally wearing Georgia my room is literally Georgia
I literally have a stand arrow my life is pretty much Georgia why I don't know
I love it so naturally I wanted to go so I constantly them ask you them hey can I come and film for the event
Before it opens and they said yes and I also wasn't told anything so I didn't know anything about this before
I got there and essentially the pop-up stores run for about two months each and then they move
So currently it's in Tokyo and then it's gonna move to Osaka and then presumably it's gone
And so when we got there they basically just told us a bit about it told us what we can do told us what we can't do and most of you have
Pretty never been press for anything but essentially you turn up
They basically lecture you for about 10 15 minutes letting you know hey don't film this please film this
Please don't say this please don't say that the usual stuff and then all
The staff were kind enough to give us a tour around the area showing is all this stuff that you can buy
All the possible merchandise that you can win in the little raffles
And I'll show you guys all the events when I'm going through them
But to give you a brief explanation of what they are the first three part part one two and three had kind of quick time
Esk things for a raffle
Basically a raffle with extra steps in geogify and there's a bunch of items that you can get and of course
It's Japan so it's Gatchify, it's all randomized these geotrophiggers are really cool
I wanted to buy them you can also buy portraits of your husband
This is something I can kind of get behind
I do I do kind of want to picture of geogile my desk not gonna lie
Oh, it's not everyone's saying so Japan does this thing called an Ichiban kuchi and essentially one of those is that you buy a ticket and you get a raffle
And on that raffle is a to e or however far down it goes and normally a is the best so here with these figures
They basically don't part one being a part two being b look at that plate
They need a geotio wine glasses, I was like sturm a geotio wine glasses
And of course every single pop up store or cafe or anything has to have its own
Thiend food and drink I wish I remembered what it was but it looks good
I think again, I'm gonna be honest again. I normally avoid the food in cafes
I normally prefer to just go to an actual restaurant, but hey, some people love it
I don't already give a fuck it does actually look pretty good in this one not just saying that x and bias this charger
I think it looks good. I did it
So here we have right these are acrylic stands, but if you look very closely at them
There's two slots so you can either put the geogio world little sign there or if you're into that
Sources BL you can put your preferred shit on both the acrylic stands and have them in one stand great
I want deal and dear so naturally any good world or place that has attractions has mini games mini games is a very generous term
And luckily geogio world is no exception to this as we have so many games over here
If you've seen Paul one of the anime, this will look very familiar to you if you haven't seen the anime, don't worry
But essentially there's a scene where you have to get the fraud and you'll get a prize based on how you perform with hitting the fraud
So give it a shot
That was the weakest most of the naming punch in my life very exciting stuff. I got to see that's like the worst
Normally you'd get a prize based on different kind of value based on which letter you got
Obviously abing the highest and see being the worst so I did actually get the worst
I think it's a really cool concept. I just wish there was some input into it
You guys know me. I love skill based games. I am a gamer guys and I love it when my games reward me for doing something
I hate randomness so not gonna lie as cool as it is to punch a frog and get a prize for it
I wish there was some way that I get influence it and the prize that I get there is another attraction here from part two
Which is spinning a wheel so I just spin it and we get a little orb with a prize
No, I see it again. I'm so cursed if you've made it this far in the video already
You're probably thinking wow this is not really that cool
It does get cool a later on the better stuff is in part four part five part three
It's just a shame that the first many games are kind of like last term my opinion, but it's still cool if you're a judge
Fair thing you know a judge your fan you put a 90 what's going on a grown man
You punch the toy frog and turn the wheel and it's happy about it
I got the worst prize again, so these two have the same prizes and see being the worst
You get this clear files just pictures basically
You get just PNGs we got we got Rob both you can tell I'm very happy about it next time
I want to get like an actual prize but luckily for me there's many games
I luckily this one right here. We're from part three
So the next kind of mini game slash quick time event as I'd call it is a reference to part three in the anime
There's a character called Joseph who can put his hands on a TV break it and it'll give him the information that he needs
Essentially if you haven't seen the anime so now I'm channeling my energy to find deer
That's where I got to see
Oh
Oh, okay not that not bad. It wasn't the worst which is see as you've already seen we've covered parts one through three attractions
But of course there's more and over here we have run kishibaze house where he draws his manga which is another
mini game attraction
All right, okay, so I just pressed up this was a bit unfortunate because we weren't actually allowed to record any of the audio or film much of it
As they wanted it to be a surprise and now here is me voicing out a very quick recreation of what happened
Oh, are you oh?
You're like Jojo? Huh?
Well, let me ask you a few questions about Jojo if you one day developed powers would use them for good
Or evil then you have to choose but we're blind or really you choose evil huh?
Would you tell your friends and family if you gained powers?
Interesting you wouldn't if you're homey went to hug you, but you're wearing socks on is it still considered get it?
They're I'm going to pretend we never had this conversation and you won't remember any of it
But I'll remember you fondly that's an extreme memeified TLDR of what happened
It was about 20 minutes of brand new dialogue that was recorded specifically for the subtraction by the voice actors
Just did like do like a personality test and this was 20 minutes of just the root that I got so I'm assuming there's more roots and more stuff
And if you're a Jojo fan and a huge one of that this is gonna be awesome because you basically get to have a Jojo character
Ask you questions and figure out your personality and that's so freaking cool
And I wish I could have shared you some of it in the video. So this is the world tour attraction and this is from pop
There obviously so I'm gonna be going to Egypt with the boys and maybe going find dear
So if you don't know the plot to part three of the anime don't worry essentially it's five of our boys
Going on a journey together to beat the evil deal and the series is laid out in the kind of monster of the weak
system as they progress from Japan all the way to Egypt by land and boat and all of that interesting stuff
And they have so many enemies along the way. Oh no it's a visual model
So currently it's just recapping the story of part three letting us know what's going on
So you spin this roulette wheel and depending on what number you get you go that many spaces and you need to go
Ex amount of spaces to get to deer and depending on which spot you land on is which stand battle you be quiz about
We're fighting the monkey and you bet your boy got the chimpanzee right away
You don't be monkey man and I don't know if you can see it but essentially there is two monitors
So one up here and one down here which is a touch screen where the answers were presented
I got it right. I think it's asking what was the missing word
I didn't know what it was asking I just yes
I've not yet what the first question was asking because it was very fast
I didn't have time to prepare so I picked one and luckily I got it right
So now we have another relatt will oh my god this is so fast
So I should move to get to Egypt or roll to Egypt. Yes, yes, you do con
So it's like if you're knowledge of the show is good you can pass this that makes sense. Okay, all right
Okay, we're finally at Egypt when go boingo amazing sand battle. Okay
I think what shape should be right for the water to the device
I think I got it wrong. I got it right. I guess I did not know what that was so hard
It was 10 seconds so not all of the questions were knowledge about the show
For example the only go boingo fight like this one just asked me to put the correct maze in between this box here
I don't know I did not much time but I got it right so who cares? All right we're against the
Great sound effects fantastic very very very
We did it. Yes, there's no final question. We did be dear
Okay, I guess I was so knowledgeable about jerseys that I want to shot dear very easily
Thank you for playing game clear. Wow. We did that. That was easy off
Jojo pathologists clearly too excessive. We're just too good and there was a reason to beat
Do because if you actually did do it you got an exclusive
Status crusaders pull the right and let's be honest. You know your boy got it
I was a bit disappointed that there wasn't a final battle against deo as I wanted some kind of budget family and few to get my boy
Do you know but whatever comment all of them I think I'm off. Oh my god. Oh wow. It's got more on the back
It's got all of the cards. That's so cool. It's the picture that they always have in the show
I kind of fanboy. That's pretty epic. These are the tarot cards and I'm not gonna lie. I think it's pretty awesome
You get every single tarot card from par three which I think is really cool just to playing even if you lose
So you know I mean I can't complain that's pretty fat ass. I love that again
If you're not a big fan of the show probably me fanboying over all this stuff is just like
What what is this grown man getting a happy about it? He's literally going around a store
So we have one final attraction and that is the passion a part five attraction
So I'm excited to see what this is because I have no idea apparently it's a test of sorts
So I'll find out what kind of passion and remember or test that I'm doing so naturally my
Jampons and things skills are pretty poor. I'm okay a little bit
But I have to use a hundred and ten percent of my brain but I've only had one hour sleep
So I'll see how this goes. I'm gonna try and join my share and air and essentially have this attraction work
Is that it would start off by asking a bunch of questions about your personality for example because I have an email
Do you want to be a leader?
Yes, I do. I would think so. What do you say yourself confident?
Little too much. Do you want people to acknowledge you as soon as possible? Oh wow that's
You can't do you? Oh my god. I mean, I mean sure. I mean who does it right questions along those lines
They ask about 20 plus in total and then based on those results a character from the show will email you now based on my results
I got emailed and called by your boy
Bootsho ready. I love that man. He's my wife who meant and if you don't know who that is best mom, but you're adding
Are booteraddies calling me what's it? I wish you guys could hear me already. I'm telling you the team leader
You see her. He's telling me these are the team members already that he has
Let's just tell me if like a little bit of the back stories of the characters. You said I'm even
I did like that part and once you've been chosen by your selected gang member man that sounds weird
This hell loud you get an email with pictures from the show that kind of like you know like scout out like oh
Yeah, so what's going on in the show? You know, yeah, we're gonna scout out the enemy and they just screenshots in the show
And after you've looked at those you do a jigsaw puzzle
I guess
Under a time limit. Not pretty that hard. It's a jigsaw puzzle. Are we even doing email now? So click the new link. Oh, it's a jigsaw
How's that what wait? Why do why is this part of the test? This is like I was literally a two-year-old right now
Needless to say I'm very thrilled about doing a jigsaw puzzle. I'm on my video to five that's zero volt
That's quite comfortable and finally after the call happens
It has a kind of Tom Cruise mission impossible self-destruct moment and you have 60 seconds to go through the PC and
Look at all the information that you're presented. That's pretty cool shut down 60 seconds. Oh, I have no idea what I'm looking for
Not really okay cool, so normally I'm not supposed to see this information about because I'm on the team
I can see the stills of the enemy
It's just a lot of the sorry PC shut down now
You basically just told me about all the characters in the gang and told me their strengths and weaknesses and just sounded hot in my air
Cuz that man's voice actor is just oh
Shucks so I guess based on which answers you give
You'll get different calls from different characters because I saw that other people were calling from different characters
Amazing deductions skills kind of that is indeed how it works. I wish I could understand more
But essentially he was just telling me about the team and what type of you know
Carried as they have in the team and I'm guessing based on the answer that you give in the first part
You might get called by Mr or you might get called by Fugur depends on who you are most like
I assume based on your answers and there's up to 13 different scenarios
So you can have 13 different conversations and what's cool is that none of these lines being reused from the enemy
It's all being recorded new just for this so it's like a whole new Jojo experience as you can go in this as many times as you want
I experience every other character which is pretty cool and obviously if you come to Jojo
Well, that isn't just the attractions over there. They're actually some games over here now if you haven't seen this game
It's essentially Jojo about it right out. It's Jojo font no
That's what it is. It is pretty fun though. I have played it a bunch. It's just kind of expensive
Like a full box is to play one round against people and most people are really bad at the game so it's really easy
Just win but I'm not kidding. So if you played Fortnite you kind of get how to play this
So any modern battle royale is literally that just with Jojo you get dropped off in Mariocha and you essentially have to just pick a character
I think this row hand duo
Jojo pretty much every character like main steak character in Jojo and you just fight each other and it's not playable right now
I would play it for you. Hopefully there's some footage on screen. It's fun. Please try it out
You will not regret it. It's a lot of fun. Please play with your friends
So there you have it. This has been Jojo world obviously if you're not a big Jojo fan
You won't find much to like here but if you're a big fan of the show and love everything around it as much as I do
You'll probably find something that will tickle your fancy here. That's for sure
Compunching frogs to having quizzes testing your knowledge of Jojo. There's something for every Jojo fan here
If you are in the Yo-Kamai area, I do recommend coming here
I don't know if I'd make a trip all the way from the US just to come here but if you're here you may
So check it out without further ado like comment subscribe and all that fun stuff
I'm gonna go home and sleep because I'm very tires right now as you might be able to tell so yeah
All right bye bye. I'm going bye
But I'm curious you as the viewer what do you think are your huge show Jofan? Do you want to go here?
You don't give a f- about Jojo and have no idea and don't give a f- about going here just tell me
What do you think? I'm genuinely curious please let me know down below just tell me like the level of Jojo fan you are and if you think this
Look even remotely interesting to you and if you don't think it looks interesting at all
I won't be offended. I don't care. I just want to make this video and show off what I thought was kind of neat
Could have been better but anyway
You